<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://anubis-rs.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://anubis-rs.org/" rel="alternate" type="text/html"/><updated>2021-10-29T21:50:59+00:00</updated><id>https://anubis-rs.org/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Anubis</title><subtitle>Anubis is a PS Vita emulator written in Rust. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome To Anubis</title><link href="https://anubis-rs.org/blog/welcome-to-anubis" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome To Anubis"/><published>2021-10-29T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-10-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://anubis-rs.org/blog/welcome-to-anubis</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://anubis-rs.org/blog/welcome-to-anubis">&lt;p&gt;Hello! My name is Lockna and I am the initiator of Anubis. Anubis is a learning project for me to learn concepts of dynamic recompilation and GPU emulation, but I invite everyone to contribute to Anubis.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this blog I will do status updates every now and then when major milestones are reached. If the project grows to a point where people are contributing on their own, I will also try to write a monthly progress report. Due to my limited time I’m not able to work actively on Anubis all the time (and of course there are times when I’m not as motivated as in other times). Nevertheless I hope to learn a lot of new things through Anubis. Also I want to create a community with Anubis where everything is about console hacking, emulation or just about game consoles. I’m also considering reversing and reimplementing the PS Vita operating system (again for the learning effect), but I’ll wait a little longer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Feel free to join our &lt;a href=&quot;https://discord.gg/Kphvzgwdkz&quot;&gt;Discord server&lt;/a&gt; and say hello, we are happy about every new face!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello! My name is Lockna and I am the initiator of Anubis. Anubis is a learning project for me to learn concepts of dynamic recompilation and GPU emulation, but I invite everyone to contribute to Anubis.</summary></entry></feed>